ANTONIO NIÑO

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

Email:

antoniocalamaco14@gmail. com

GitHub: github.com/jossnc

Location: Mexico

I am a software engineer who loves his job and I have a passion for what I do. I have 3 years of experience in software development, I have worked in different companies, businesses and freelancer. I code in JavaScript, C#, React and just about any language or framework I find right for the project. In my beginnings I work in web and UI/UX design. Today I work on Web Applications, Mobile Apps, Responsive Design.

SKILLS

ReactJs, ReactNative, JavaScript, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Express, API REST, Git, Linux, MySQL, PostgreSQL, WordPress, NodeJs, NextJs, Redux.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Servicios Publicos, Gomez Palacio, DGO. MX Full Stack Developer

2022 - currently

- Front-end development using multiple languages and frameworks, including JavaScript, React Native, ReactJs and Express.
- Experience in creating web solutions for multiple clients, ensuring high-quality, efficient, and scalable applications.

Lujan Solutions, Torreon, COAH. MX Full Stack Developer

2021 - 2022

- - Development of web pages and modules for business and companies. web design, API REST.
 - Use of languages and technologies: HTML, CSS, Bootstrap and JavaScript to create web pages and app website

Freelancer 2020 - currently

I worked in different projects for clients, local business, schools. I made web pages, web applications, support. I used technologies such as Html, css, wordpress, react, JavaScript

EDUCATION		
Cert	FreeCodeCamp JavaScript Algorithms and Data Structures	2022
Cert	FreeCodeCam Web Responsive	2022
Engr	Instituto Tecnologico de Torreon, Systems engineering	2016 - 2022